mybb3.org 2008-06-03

# MakeForum.org - Privacy Policy

**MakeForum.org Privacy Policy**

MakeForum.org has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this website. Please note that this privacy policy only covers the website here at makeforum.org, the individual forums that are hosted by us control there own privacy policies.

**Information Automatically Logged**

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our website. The IP address is not displayed anywhere on the website, and is not disclosed to any other parties. The IP address is also used if it becomes neccessary to ban a member of the forums and to stop them from re-registering with another alias.

**Cookies**

This site uses cookies to store the login information of registered forum members, visitors preferences, record session information.

**Forms**

Our site's forms requires users to give us contact information (like their name, email, etc). This contact information is only used to get in touch with the member in the event of a forum rule violation.

**External Links**

This site contains links to other sites. However, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any such websites. We do however have moderators for each forum, who will delete/edit any links, content, etc that they feel should not be printed in any of the forums.

**Security**

We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site. 

**Contacting Us**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, you can contact the administrator using the contact us form.  
If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by or we do not send newsletters.

IF THE PRIVACY POLICY DESCRIBED HERE ARE NOT FULLY ACCEPTABLE, YOU MUST IMMEDIATELY TERMINATE YOUR USE OF THIS WEB SITE.
